Did you see this video where a black writer for the show The Bear had the cops called on him because this white woman didn't like the way he was sitting?
Listen to this.
The one black dude on the train because this white woman said she didn't like the way I was sitting on the train.
So you call the police.
You call the police to arrest the one black dude on the train.
I am.
I haven't done anything illegal.
I am sitting on a train and one white woman didn't like my presence resisting what resisting what what are you what are you trying to arrest me for?
I was sitting on a train.
I was sitting on a train and you're trying to arrest me for what?
I not even know what you're trying to arrest her for because a white woman is not resisting.
Resisting what?
This happened to Alex O'Keefe who has been a writer on The Bear and he's also been a speechwriter for people like Elizabeth Warren.
And according to reports and Alex's own accounts he was on a train going to Connecticut.
He was sitting minding his own business when she got on and started to complain about the way he was sitting.
When Alex refused she went to the conductor and the conductor called the police.
And as they were waiting for the police to arrive one of the people that was with the old lady told Alex you're not the minority anymore.
Alex was taken off the train.
He was handcuffed and questioned for a while.
But then when he reminded them that he was not given a lawyer and that the cops didn't even talk to the old white woman and get her statement that's when they let him go.
And just a reminder this is what white people do.
They weaponize the police this way.
There was a time in this country where any white person could tell any person of color especially black people hey go to the store for me.
And if they didn't they could call the cops on a black kid for not going to the store for them.
And it seems like we're right back there that if a black person does not sit up straight any white person can call the cops on them.
And the cops will come and happily oblige.
And this is nothing against Alex he seems like a great person but I'm talking about people who think that if you're good enough and you do everything right and you're exceptional that white people will accept you.
Alex seems exceptional but unfortunately any white person can strip a person of color all that all they have to do is call the police and say he's sitting wrong.
And if in any way you're feeling sorry for this old lady like oh look at her maybe she was confused maybe she didn't know no she knew exactly what she was doing.
I'm sure this isn't the first time she's weaponized the police against a black body or any person of color.
We still don't know who she is but does it matter because we live in such a fucked up system that anybody can do this.
I'm really sorry this happened to Alex I really do hope he's okay and I'm just wondering how and when will we get to the point where white people can't fucking do this to us anymore.